SEAN MILFORT

System Administrator II

seanmilfort@me.com
New Cumberland, PA
seanmilfort.com
linkedin.com/in/seanmilfort
blog.seanmilfort.com
@SeanMilfort
@SeanMilfort

@SeanMilfort

Summary

System Administrator II with 6+ years of experience implementing new solutions and strategies in multiple organizations. Passion for development work and learning different languages for building side projects during free time. Currently working on a master's degree for Computer Information Science.

Work Experience

Rite Aid | Camp Hill, PA

System Administrator II

- Maintaining AirWatch MDM Environment for 10,000+ devices
- Developing/Testing New Technologies for Store Environment

WellSpan Health | York, PA

System Administrator

December 2019 - September 2021

September 2021 - Present

September 2021 - Present

December 2019 - September 2021

- Creating/Developing Application Packages & Software Installations for mass/minor deployments
- Creating Technical/Support Documentation for new & existing solutions
- Evaluating/Designing Technical Solutions to improve End User Workflow
- Developing/Troubleshooting Mobile Device Management Solutions (AirWatch)
- Maintaining/Improving IT Environment with new Technological Improvements

Burlington Stores, Inc. | Burlington, NJ

IT Integration Analyst II

April 2015 - November 2019

November 2017 - November 2019

- Responsible for large-scale Engineering/Design changes to our Mobile Device Management Platform
- (AirWatch) containing 11,000+ devices (iOS, Android & Windows CE)
 Created Installer/Scripting Packages for silent installations for 15,000 Machine (Unix Scripting, PowerShell)
- & Bash)
- Developed/Maintained the Base Computer Image for 4,000+ machines (Windows/Mac)
- Created/Edited/Deployed Group Policy 15,000+ active devices
- Evaluated/Met with Senior Business Partners/Vendors on multiple different initiatives

IT Integration Analyst I

April 2017 - November 2017

- Implemented/Led Microsoft Surface Project in Corporate/Field Environment
- Planned/Integrated New Technology into Current Environment
- Maintained/Deployed Bi-Quarterly Updates to 4,000+ Machines
- Handled Maintenance/Support/Upgrades of Mobile Device Management Product (AirWatch) containing 11,000+ active devices
- Researched/Suggested Solutions to improve Productivity/Performance

IT Integration Associate

October 2016 - April 2017

- Helped Create/Set the company standard for Corporate Level Devices (Windows/Mac)
- Created Mobile profiles and packages for iOS Devices in Corporate/Store Environment for 4,000+ Mobile **Devices**
- Authored/Maintained Support and Procedural Documentation for Support Teams
- Created/Deployed Software Packages on large scale for Endpoints (Windows/Mac)

Client Technologies Technician I

April 2015 - October 2016

- Supported/Troubleshooted Windows and Mac Machines on a large scale
- Participated in many different with various projects with different departments in IT
- Supported Mobile Devices (iPad and iPhones) while utilizing AirWatch as MDM tool
- Basic Network troubleshooting and configuration (DNS, VLAN, Connectivity)
- Delivered Customer Service to Troubleshoot and Enhance End User Experience

Skills

Languages JavaScript HTML & CSS PowerShell

OS Management (Windows, macOS, Android, Linux & iOS) Mobile Device Management Active Directory & Group Policy Management Large Scale Packaging & Deployment **Bash Scripting** Microsoft Deployment Toolkit

Infrastructure Skills

Interpersonal Skills

Leadership **Teamwork Technical Documentation Customer Service** Communication

Awards

CIO Award

Dennis Hodgson, CIO, Burlington Stores, Inc. April 2018

CEO Award

Thomas Kingsbury, CEO, Burlington Stores, Inc. September 2017

Education

La Salle University, Expected Graduation in 2022 Master of Science (M.S.), Computer Information Science

Philadelphia, PA

La Salle University, 2015

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Computer Science

Philadelphia, PA